A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "Choice of Antibacterial Drugs When Infecting Organisms Have Not Been Identified" 8:57, Issue 197, 1966 July 29; 2 of 3 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- "Choice of Antibacterial Drugs When Infecting Organisms Have Not Been Identified" 8:57, Issue 197, 1966 July 29; 3 of 3 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- "Microorganisms Most Likely to Cause Infection" 8:60, Issue 197, 1966 July 29; 1 of 2 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- "Microorganisms Most Likely to Cause Infection" 8:60, Issue 197, 1966 July 29; 2 of 2 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- "Ovulen - A New Oral Contraceptive" 8:61, Issue 198, 1966 August 12; 1 of 3 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- "Ovulen - A New Oral Contraceptive [Sources, Reprints]" 8:61, Issue 198, 1966 August 12; 2 of 3 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- "Ovulen - A New Oral Contraceptive [Sources, Reprints]" 8:61, Issue 198, 1966 August 12; 3 of 3 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- "Stat-Test for Bacteriuria" 8:62, Issue 198, 1966 August 12; 1 of 2 (Box 108, Folder 9)
- "Stat-Test for Bacteriuria [Sources, Reprints]" 8:62, Issue 198, 1966 August 12; 2 of 2 (Box 108, Folder 10)
- "Treatment of Respiratory Insufficiency" 8:63, Issue 198, 1966 August 12; 1 of 4 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- "Treatment of Respiratory Insufficiency" 8:63, Issue 198, 1966 August 12; 2 of 4 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- "Treatment of Respiratory Insufficiency [Manufacturers' Information]" 8:63, Issue 198, 1966 August 12; 3 of 4 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- "Treatment of Respiratory Insufficiency [Sources, Reprints]" 8:63, Issue 198, 1966 August 12; 4 of 4 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- "Clinical Significance of Serum Binding of Antibiotics" unpublished, 1966; 1 of 2 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- "Clinical Significance of Serum Binding of Antibiotics" unpublished, 1966; 2 of 2 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- "Panalba and Novobiocin" 8:65, Issue 199, 1966 August 26; 1 of 2 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- "Panalba and Novobiocin" 8:65, Issue 199, 1966 August 26; 2 of 2 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- "Drugs for Cardiac Arrhythmias Associated With Myocardial Infarction" 8:66, Issue 199, 1966 August 26; 1 of 3 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- "Drugs for Cardiac Arrhythmias Associated With Myocardial Infarction" 8:66, Issue 199, 1966 August 26; 2 of 3 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- "Drugs for Cardiac Arrhythmias Associated With Myocardial Infarction [Sources, Reprints]" 8:66, Issue 199, 1966 August 26; 3 of 3 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- "The Choice of Therapy in the Treatment of Cancer" 8:69, Issue 200, 1966 September 9; 1 of 6 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- "The Choice of Therapy in the Treatment of Cancer" 8:69, Issue 200, 1966 September 9; 2 of 6 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- "The Choice of Therapy in the Treatment of Cancer" 8:69, Issue 200, 1966 September 9; 3 of 6 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- "The Choice of Therapy in the Treatment of Cancer" 8:69, Issue 200, 1966 September 9; 4 of 6 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- "The Choice of Therapy in the Treatment of Cancer - Manufacturers' Replies" 8:69, Issue 200, 1966 September 9; 5 of 6 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- "The Choice of Therapy in the Treatment of Cancer [Sources, Reprints]" 8:69, Issue 200, 1966 September 9; 6 of 6 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- "Tolinase - A New Oral Antidiabetic Drug" 8:77, Issue 201, 1966 September 23; 1 of 2 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- "Tolinase - A New Oral Antidiabetic Drug [Manufacturers' Replies]" 8:77, Issue 201, 1966 September 23; 2 of 2 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- "Influenza Immunization" 8:78, Issue 201, 1966 September 23 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- "Gonococcal Infections" 8:79, Issue 201, 1966 September 23; 1 of 3 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- "Gonococcal Infections" 8:79, Issue 201, 1966 September 23; 2 of 3 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- "Gonococcal Infections [Sources, Reprints]" 8:79, Issue 201, 1966 September 23; 3 of 3 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- "Intrauterine Contraceptive Devices" 8:81, Issue 202, 1966 October 7; 1 of 5 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- "Intrauterine Contraceptive Devices" 8:81, Issue 202, 1966 October 7; 2 of 5 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- "Intrauterine Contraceptive Devices" 8:81, Issue 202, 1966 October 7; 3 of 5 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- "Intrauterine Contraceptive Devices [Sources, Reprints]" 8:81, Issue 202, 1966 October 7; 4 of 5 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- "Intrauterine Contraceptive Devices [Sources, Reprints]" 8:81, Issue 202, 1966 October 7; 5 of 5 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- "Nocturnal or Recumbency Muscle Cramps" 8:83, Issue 202, 1966 October 7; 1 of 2 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- "Nocturnal or Recumbency Muscle Cramps" 8:83, Issue 202, 1966 October 7; 2 of 2 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- "Amniocentesis and Intrauterine Fetal Transfusion in Erythroblastosis Fetalis" 8:85, Issue 203, 1966 October 21; 1 of 2 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- "Amniocentesis and Intrauterine Fetal Transfusion in Erythroblastosis Fetalis" 8:85, Issue 203, 1966 October 21; 2 of 2 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- "Unopettes" 8:86, Issue 203, 1966 October 21; 1 of 3 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- "Unopettes [Sources, Reprints]" 8:86, Issue 203, 1966 October 21; 2 of 3 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- "Unopettes [Sources, Reprints]" 8:86, Issue 203, 1966 October 21; 3 of 3 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- "Anthraquinone Laxatives" 8:87, Issue 203, 1966 October 21; 1 of 2 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- "Anthraquinone Laxatives [Sources, Reprints]" 8:87, Issue 203, 1966 October 21; 2 of 2 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- "Turbinaire" 8:89, Issue 204, 1966 November 4; 1 of 2 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- "Turbinaire" 8:89, Issue 204, 1966 November 4; 2 of 2 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- "Trocinate and Valpin" 8:90, issue 204, 1966 November 4 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- "Determination of Ovulation Time and the Rhythm Method of Contraception" 8:91, Issue 204, 1966 November 4; 1 of 2 (Box 112, Folder 9)
- "Determination of Ovulation Time and the Rhythm Method of Contraception [Sources, Reprints]" 8:91, Issue 204, 1966 November 4; 1 of 2 (Box 112, Folder 10)
- "Rondomycin" 8:93, Issue 205, 1966 November 18; 1 of 3 (Box 112, Folder 11)
- "Rondomycin [Sources, Reprints]" 8:93, Issue 205, 1966 November 18; 2 of 3 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- "Rondomycin [Sources, Reprints]" 8:93, Issue 205, 1966 November 18; 3 of 3 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- "Sansert" 8:94, Issue 205, 1966 November 18; 1 of 3 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- "Sansert [Sources, Reprints]" 8:94, Issue 205, 1966 November 18; 2 of 3 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- "Sansert [Sources, Reprints]" 8:94, Issue 205, 1966 November 18; 3 of 3 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- "Mono-Test" 8:95, Issue 205, 1966 November 18 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- "Citanest - A Local Anesthetic" 8:97, Issue 206, 1966 December 2; 1 of 4 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- "Citanest - A Local Anesthetic [Sources, Reprints]" 8:97, Issue 206, 1966 December 2; 2 of 4 (Box 113, Folder 8)
- "Citanest - A Local Anesthetic [Sources, Reprints]" 8:97, Issue 206, 1966 December 2; 3 of 4 (Box 113, Folder 9)
- "Citanest - A Local Anesthetic [Sources, Reprints]" 8:97, Issue 206, 1966 December 2; 4 of 4 (Box 113, Folder 10)
- "Zyloprim and Other Drugs in the Management of Gout" 8:98, Issue 206, 1966 December 2; 1 of 3 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- "Zyloprim and Other Drugs in the Management of Gout" 8:98, Issue 206, 1966 December 2; 2 of 3 (Box 114, Folder 2)
- "Zyloprim and Other Drugs in the Management of Gout [Sources, Reprints]" 8:98, Issue 206, 1966 December 2; 3 of 3 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- "Fluorescein Tests for Localizing Gastrointestinal Bleeding" 8:100, Issue 206, 1966 December 2; 1 of 2 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- "Fluorescein Tests for Localizing Gastrointestinal Bleeding" 8:100, Issue 206, 1966 December 2; 2 of 2 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- "A New Tetracycline Formulation" 8:101, Issue 207, 1966 December 16; 1 of 4 (Box 114, Folder 6)
- "A New Tetracycline Formulation" 8:101, Issue 207, 1966 December 16; 2 of 4 (Box 114, Folder 7)
- "A New Tetracycline Formulation [Sources, Reprints]" 8:101, Issue 207, 1966 December 16; 3 of 4 (Box 114, Folder 8)
- "A New Tetracycline Formulation [Sources, Reprints]" 8:101, Issue 207, 1966 December 16; 4 of 4 (Box 114, Folder 9)
- "Detection of Proteinuria" 8:103, Issue 207, 1966 December 17 (Box 114, Folder 10)
- "The Prevention of Urinary Calculi-I" 8:103, Issue 207, 1966 December 17; 1 of 6 (Box 114, Folder 11)
- "The Prevention of Urinary Calculi-I" 8:103, Issue 207, 1966 December 17; 2 of 6 (Box 114, Folder 12)
- "The Prevention of Urinary Calculi-I" 8:103, Issue 207, 1966 December 17; 3 of 6 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- "The Prevention of Urinary Calculi-I [Sources, Reprints]" 8:103, Issue 207, 1966 December 17; 4 of 6 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- "The Prevention of Urinary Calculi-I [Sources, Reprints]" 8:103, Issue 207, 1966 December 17; 5 of 6 (Box 115, Folder 3)
- "The Prevention of Urinary Calculi-I [Sources, Reprints]" 8:103, Issue 207, 1966 December 17; 6 of 6 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- "The Fogarty Catheterand Thromboembolism" 8:105, Issue 208, 1966 December 30; 1 of 2 (Box 115, Folder 5)
- "The Fogarty Catheterand Thromboembolism" 8:105, Issue 208, 1966 December 30; 2 of 2 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- "Choice of Method for the Measurement of SGOT" 8:106, Issue 208, 1966 December 30 (Box 115, Folder 7)
- "Clinical Significance of Plasma Protein Binding of Antibiotics" 8:107, Issue 208, 1966 December 30; 1 of 2 (Box 115, Folder 8)
- "Clinical Significance of Plasma Protein Binding of Antibiotics" 8:107, Issue 208, 1966 December 30; 1 of 2 (Box 115, Folder 9)
- "LSD" 9:1, Issue 209, 1967 January 13 (Box 115, Folder 10)
- "Human Chorionic Gonadotropin (HCG) " 9:2, Issue 209, 1967 January 13; 1 of 2 (Box 115, Folder 11)
- "Human Chorionic Gonadotropin (HCG) [Sources, Reprints]" 9:2, Issue 209, 1967 January 13; 2 of 2 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- "Newer Serum Enzyme Determinations as Aids in Diagnosis" 9:3, Issue 209, 1967 January 13; 1 of 3 (Box 116, Folder 2)
- "Newer Serum Enzyme Determinations as Aids in Diagnosis" 9:3, Issue 209, 1967 January 13; 2 of 3 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- "Newer Serum Enzyme Determinations as Aids in Diagnosis [Sources, Reprints]" 9:3, Issue 209, 1967 January 13; 3 of 3 (Box 116, Folder 4)
- "Symmetrel - A New 'Antiviral' Agent" 9:5, Issue 210, 1967 January 27; 1 of 2 (Box 116, Folder 5)
- "Symmetrel - A New 'Antiviral' Agent" 9:5, Issue 210, 1967 January 27; 1 of 2 (Box 116, Folder 6)
- "Lasix" 9:6, Issue 210, 1967 January 27; 1 of 5 (Box 116, Folder 7)
- "Lasix" 9:6, Issue 210, 1967 January 27; 2 of 5 (Box 116, Folder 8)
- "Lasix [Sources, Reprints]" 9:6, Issue 210, 1967 January 27; 3 of 5 (Box 116, Folder 9)
- "Lasix [Sources, Reprints]" 9:6, Issue 210, 1967 January 27; 4 of 5 (Box 116, Folder 10)
- "Lasix [Sources, Reprints]" 9:6, Issue 210, 1967 January 27; 5 of 5 (Box 116, Folder 11)
- "Cycloplasmol in Peripheral and Cerebral Vascular Disease" 9:9, Issue 211, 1967 February 10; 1 of 3 (Box 116, Folder 12)
- "Cycloplasmol in Peripheral and Cerebral Vascular Disease" 9:9, Issue 211, 1967 February 10; 2 of 3 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- "Cycloplasmol in Peripheral and Cerebral Vascular Disease [Sources, Reprints]" 9:9, Issue 211, 1967 February 10; 3 of 3 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- "Amicar and Hyperfibrinolysis" 9:10, Issue 211, 1967 February 10; 1 of 6 (Box 117, Folder 3)
- "Amicar and Hyperfibrinolysis" 9:10, Issue 211, 1967 February 10; 2 of 6 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- "Amicar and Hyperfibrinolysis [Sources, Reprints]" 9:10, Issue 211, 1967 February 10; 3 of 6 (Box 117, Folder 5)
- "Amicar and Hyperfibrinolysis [Sources, Reprints]" 9:10, Issue 211, 1967 February 10; 4 of 6 (Box 117, Folder 6)
- "Amicar and Hyperfibrinolysis [Sources, Reprints]" 9:10, Issue 211, 1967 February 10; 5 of 6 (Box 117, Folder 7)
- "Amicar and Hyperfibrinolysis [Sources, Reprints]" 9:10, Issue 211, 1967 February 10; 6 of 6 (Box 117, Folder 8)
- "Dip Tests for Glycosuria" 9:12, Issue 211, 1967 February 10 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  {Note: 'Sources, Resources' material for 9:12 in box 180}.
- "Deprol Advertising" 9:13, Issue 212, 1967 February 24; 1 of 5 (Box 117, Folder 10)
- "Deprol Advertising" 9:13, Issue 212, 1967 February 24; 2 of 5 (Box 117, Folder 11)
- "Deprol Advertising [Sources, Reprints]" 9:13, Issue 212, 1967 February 24; 1 of 5 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- "Deprol Advertising [Sources, Reprints]" 9:13, Issue 212, 1967 February 24; 2 of 5 (Box 118, Folder 2)
- "Deprol Advertising [Sources, Reprints]" 9:13, Issue 212, 1967 February 24; 3 of 5 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- "Nitrofurazone - A Topical Antimicrobial Drug" 9:15, Issue 212, 1967 February 24; 1 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- "Nitrofurazone - A Topical Antimicrobial Drug" 9:15, Issue 212, 1967 February 24; 2 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- "Nitrofurazone - A Topical Antimicrobial Drug [Sources, Reprints]" 9:15, Issue 212, 1967 February 24; 3 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 6)
- "Elase and Other Proteolytic Enzyme Drugs" 9:17, Issue 213, 1967 March 10; 1 of 6 (Box 118, Folder 7)
- "Elase and Other Proteolytic Enzyme Drugs" 9:17, Issue 213, 1967 March 10; 2 of 6 (Box 118, Folder 8)
- "Elase and Other Proteolytic Enzyme Drugs [Sources, Reprints]" 9:17, Issue 213, 1967 March 10; 3 of 6 (Box 118, Folder 9)
- "Elase and Other Proteolytic Enzyme Drugs [Sources, Reprints]" 9:17, Issue 213, 1967 March 10; 4 of 6 (Box 118, Folder 10)
- "Elase and Other Proteolytic Enzyme Drugs [Sources, Reprints]" 9:17, Issue 213, 1967 March 10; 5 of 6 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- "Elase and Other Proteolytic Enzyme Drugs [Sources, Reprints]" 9:17, Issue 213, 1967 March 10; 6 of 6 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- "Bioplant" 9:18, Issue 213, March 10, 1967 "Surgibone (Bioplant) - Correction" 9:32, Issue 216, April 21, 1967, 1967 March 10 1967 April 21; 1 of 3 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- "Bioplant" 9:18, Issue 213, March 10, 1967 "Surgibone (Bioplant) - Correction [Sources, Reprints]" 9:32, Issue 216, April 21, 1967, 1967 March 10 1967 April 21; 2 of 3 (Box 119, Folder 4)
- "Bioplant" 9:18, Issue 213, March 10, 1967 "Surgibone (Bioplant) - Correction [Sources, Reprints]" 9:32, Issue 216, April 21, 1967, 1967 March 10 1967 April 21; 3 of 3 (Box 119, Folder 5)
- "Urography for Urea Nitrogen Determinations" 9:20, Issue 213, 1967 March 10 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- "Correction on Canadian Certification Procedures for Tetracyclines" 9:20, Issue 213, 1967 March 10 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- "The Choice of an Oral Contraceptive" 9:21, Issue 214, 1967 March 24; 1 of 3 (Box 119, Folder 8)
- "The Choice of an Oral Contraceptive" 9:21, Issue 214, 1967 March 24; 2 of 3 (Box 119, Folder 9)
- "The Choice of an Oral Contraceptive" 9:21, Issue 214, 1967 March 24; 3 of 3 (Box 119, Folder 10)
- "Penthrane for Obstetrical Anesthesia" 9:23, Issue 214, 1967 March 24; 1 of 7 (Box 119, Folder 11)
- "Penthrane for Obstetrical Anesthesia" 9:23, Issue 214, 1967 March 24; 2 of 7 (Box 119, Folder 12)
- "Penthrane for Obstetrical Anesthesia [Sources, Reprints]" 9:23, Issue 214, 1967 March 24; 3 of 7 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- "Penthrane for Obstetrical Anesthesia [Sources, Reprints]" 9:23, Issue 214, 1967 March 24; 4 of 7 (Box 120, Folder 2)
- "Penthrane for Obstetrical Anesthesia [Sources, Reprints]" 9:23, Issue 214, 1967 March 24; 5 of 7 (Box 120, Folder 3)
- "Penthrane for Obstetrical Anesthesia [Sources, Reprints]" 9:23, Issue 214, 1967 March 24; 6 of 7 (Box 120, Folder 4)
- "Penthrane for Obstetrical Anesthesia [Sources, Reprints]" 9:23, Issue 214, 1967 March 24; 7 of 7 (Box 120, Folder 5)
- "Disinfection of Medical Equipment" 9:25, Issue 215, 1967 April 7; 1 of 3 (Box 120, Folder 6)
- "Disinfection of Medical Equipment" 9:25, Issue 215, 1967 April 7; 2 of 3 (Box 120, Folder 7)
- "Disinfection of Medical Equipment [Sources, Reprints]" 9:25, Issue 215, 1967 April 7; 3 of 3 (Box 120, Folder 8)
- "Pipobroman (Vercyte) - A New Antineoplastic Drug" 9:27, Issue 215, 1967 April 7 (Box 120, Folder 9)
- "Cyproheptadine (Periactin) for Allergic and Pruritic Dermatoses" 9:28, Issue 215, 1967 April 7; 1 of 3 (Box 120, Folder 10)
- "Cyproheptadine (Periactin) for Allergic and Pruritic Dermatoses [Sources, Reprints]" 9:28, Issue 215, 1967 April 7; 2 of 3 (Box 120, Folder 11)
- "Cyproheptadine (Periactin) for Allergic and Pruritic Dermatoses [Sources, Reprints]" 9:28, Issue 215, 1967 April 7; 3 of 3 (Box 121, Folder 1)
- "Betahistine Hydrochloride (Serc) for Meniere's Syndrome" 9:29, Issue 216, 1967 April 21; 1 of 3 (Box 121, Folder 2)
- "Betahistine Hydrochloride (Serc) for Meniere's Syndrome [Sources, Reprints]" 9:29, Issue 216, 1967 April 21; 2 of 3 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- "Betahistine Hydrochloride (Serc) for Meniere's Syndrome [Sources, Reprints]" 9:29, Issue 216, 1967 April 21; 3 of 3 (Box 121, Folder 4)
- "Antimicrobial Cold Remedies" 9:30, Issue 216, 1967 April 21 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- "Treatment of Hemorrhage in Hemophilia" 9:31, Issue 216, 1967 April 21; 1 of 2 (Box 121, Folder 6)
- "Treatment of Hemorrhage in Hemophilia" 9:31, Issue 216, 1967 April 21; 2 of 2 (Box 121, Folder 7)
- "Gentamicin (Garamycin) - A New Topical Antimicrobial Drug" 9:33, Issue 217, 1967 May 5; 1 of 2 (Box 121, Folder 8)
- "Gentamicin (Garamycin) - A New Topical Antimicrobial Drug" 9:33, Issue 217, 1967 May 5; 2 of 2 (Box 121, Folder 9)
- "Pheochromocytoma" 9:34, Issue 217, 1967 May 5; 1 of 4 (Box 122, Folder 1)
- "Pheochromocytoma" 9:34, Issue 217, 1967 May 5; 2 of 4 (Box 122, Folder 2)
- "Pheochromocytoma [Sources, Reprints]" 9:34, Issue 217, 1967 May 5; 3 of 4 (Box 122, Folder 3)
- "Pheochromocytoma [Sources, Reprints]" 9:34, Issue 217, 1967 May 5; 4 of 4 (Box 122, Folder 4)
- "Electrophoretic Studies as an Aid in Diagnosis" 9:36, Issue 217, 1967 May 5 (Box 122, Folder 5)
- "Fiorinal and Other Sedative-Analgesic Drugs for 'Tension' Headache" 9:37, Issue 218, 1967 May 19; 1 of 2 (Box 122, Folder 6)
- "Fiorinal and Other Sedative-Analgesic Drugs for 'Tension' Headache [Sources, Reprints]" 9:37, Issue 218, 1967 May 19; 2 of 2 (Box 122, Folder 7)
- "The Prevention and Medical Treatment of Urinary Calculi - II" 9:38, Issue 218, 1967 May 19; 1 of 2 (Box 122, Folder 8)
- "The Prevention and Medical Treatment of Urinary Calculi - II" 9:38, Issue 218, 1967 May 19; 2 of 2 (Box 122, Folder 9)
- "Testuria for the Detection of Bacteriuria" 9:40, Issue 218, 1967 May 19; 1 of 2 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- "Testuria for the Detection of Bacteriuria [Sources, Reprints]" 9:40, Issue 218, 1967 May 19; 2 of 2 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- "Tests of Prednisone Tablets" 9:41, Issue 219, 1967 June 2; 1 of 2 (Box 123, Folder 3)
- "Tests of Prednisone Tablets" 9:41, Issue 219, 1967 June 2; 2 of 2 (Box 123, Folder 4)
- "Achilles Reflex Time in the Diagnosis of Thyroid Disfuction" 9:43, Issue 219, 1967 June 2; 1 of 3 (Box 123, Folder 5)
- "Achilles Reflex Time in the Diagnosis of Thyroid Disfuction" 9:43, Issue 219, 1967 June 2; 2 of 3 (Box 123, Folder 6)
- "Achilles Reflex Time in the Diagnosis of Thyroid Disfuction [Sources, Reprints]" 9:43, Issue 219, 1967 June 2; 3 of 3 (Box 123, Folder 7)
- "Electrophoretic Studies as an Aid in Diagnosis - Correction" 9:44, Issue 219, 1967 June 2 (Box 123, Folder 8)
- "Atromid-S for the Reduction of Plasma Lipids" 9:45, Issue 220, 1967 June 16; 1 of 3 (Box 123, Folder 9)
- "Atromid-S for the Reduction of Plasma Lipids" 9:45, Issue 220, 1967 June 16; 2 of 3 (Box 123, Folder 10)
- "Atromid-S for the Reduction of Plasma Lipids" 9:45, Issue 220, 1967 June 16; 3 of 3 (Box 123, Folder 11)
- "Effect of pH of the Urine on Antimicrobial Therapy of Urinary Tract Infections" 9:47, Issue 220, 1967 June 16; 1 of 3 (Box 124, Folder 1)
- "Effect of pH of the Urine on Antimicrobial Therapy of Urinary Tract Infections" 9:47, Issue 220, 1967 June 16; 2 of 3 (Box 124, Folder 2)
- "Effect of pH of the Urine on Antimicrobial Therapy of Urinary Tract Infections [Sources, Reprints]" 9:47, Issue 220, 1967 June 16; 3 of 3 (Box 124, Folder 3)
- "Methotrimeprazine (Levoprome) - A Potent Analgesic" 9:49, Issue 221, 1967 June 30; 1 of 5 (Box 124, Folder 4)
- "Methotrimeprazine (Levoprome) - A Potent Analgesic" 9:49, Issue 221, 1967 June 30; 2 of 5 (Box 124, Folder 5)
- "Methotrimeprazine (Levoprome) - A Potent Analgesic [Sources, Reprints]" 9:49, Issue 221, 1967 June 30; 3 of 5 (Box 124, Folder 6)
- Issue 221, 1967 June 30; 2 of 5 (Box 124)
- "Methotrimeprazine (Levoprome) - A Potent Analgesic [Sources, Reprints]" 9:49, Issue 221, 1967 June 30; 3 of 5 (Box 124, Folder 6)
- "Methotrimeprazine (Levoprome) - A Potent Analgesic [Sources, Reprints]" 9:49, Issue 221, 1967 June 30; 4 of 5 (Box 124, Folder 7)
- "Methotrimeprazine (Levoprome) - A Potent Analgesic [Sources, Reprints]" 9:49, Issue 221, 1967 June 30; 5 of 5 (Box 124, Folder 8)
- "Penicillamine" 9:51, Issue 221, 1967 June 30; 1 of 4 (Box 124, Folder 9)
- "Penicillamine" 9:51, Issue 221, 1967 June 30; 2 of 4 (Box 124, Folder 10)
- "Penicillamine [Sources, Reprints]" 9:51, Issue 221, 1967 June 30; 3 of 4 (Box 124, Folder 11)
- "Penicillamine [Sources, Reprints]" 9:51, Issue 221, 1967 June 30; 4 of 4 (Box 124, Folder 12)
- "Ethacrynic Acid" 9:53, Issue 222, 1967 July 14; 1 of 3 (Box 125, Folder 1)
- "Ethacrynic Acid" 9:53, Issue 222, 1967 July 14; 2 of 3 (Box 125, Folder 2)
- "Ethacrynic Acid [Sources, Reprints]" 9:53, Issue 222, 1967 July 14; 3 of 3 (Box 125, Folder 3)
- "Penicillin G and Other Penicillins in the Treatment of Coccal Infections" 9:55, Issue 222, 1967 July 14; 1 of 3 (Box 125, Folder 4)
- "Penicillin G and Other Penicillins in the Treatment of Coccal Infections" 9:55, Issue 222, 1967 July 14; 2 of 3 (Box 125, Folder 5)
- "Penicillin G and Other Penicillins in the Treatment of Coccal Infections" 9:55, Issue 222, 1967 July 14; 3 of 3 (Box 125, Folder 6)
- "Peritoneal Dialysis" 9:57, Issue 223, 1967 July 28; 1 of 5 (Box 125, Folder 7)
- "Peritoneal Dialysis" 9:57, Issue 223, 1967 July 28; 2 of 5 (Box 125, Folder 8)
- "Peritoneal Dialysis [Sources, Reprints]" 9:57, Issue 223, 1967 July 28; 3 of 5 (Box 125, Folder 9)
- "Peritoneal Dialysis [Sources, Reprints]" 9:57, Issue 223, 1967 July 28; 4 of 5 (Box 125, Folder 10)
- "Peritoneal Dialysis [Sources, Reprints]" 9:57, Issue 223, 1967 July 28; 5 of 5 (Box 126, Folder 1)
- "Drugs and Other Factors Interfering With Reliability of Blood Chemistry Determination" 9:59, Issue 223, 1967 July 28; 1 of 2 (Box 126, Folder 2)
- "Drugs and Other Factors Interfering With Reliability of Blood Chemistry Determination" 9:59, Issue 223, 1967 July 28; 2 of 2 (Box 126, Folder 3)
- "Kanamycin and Neomycin" 9:61, Issue 224, 1967 August 11; 1 of 4 (Box 126, Folder 4)
- "Kanamycin and Neomycin" 9:61, Issue 224, 1967 August 11; 2 of 4 (Box 126, Folder 5)
- "Kanamycin and Neomycin" 9:61, Issue 224, 1967 August 11; 3 of 4 (Box 126, Folder 6)
- "Kanamycin and Neomycin" 9:61, Issue 224, 1967 August 11; 4 of 4 (Box 126, Folder 7)
- "Diphenylhydrantoin (Dilantin) in Cardiac Arrhythmias" 9:64, Issue 224, 1967 August 11 (Box 126, Folder 8)
- "Chlorphenesin Carbamate (Maolate) " 9:65, Issue 225, 1967 August 25; 1 of 2 (Box 126, Folder 9)
- "Chlorphenesin Carbamate (Maolate) [Sources, Reprints]" 9:65, Issue 225, 1967 August 25; 2 of 2 (Box 126, Folder 10)
- "Serum Bactericidal Test in Bacterial Endocarditis and Bacteremias" 9:66, Issue 225, 1967 August 25 (Box 127, Folder 1)
- "Incompatability of Drugs for Intravenous Administration" 9:67, Issue 225, 1967 August 25; 1 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 2)
- "Incompatability of Drugs for Intravenous Administration" 9:67, Issue 225, 1967 August 25; 2 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 3)
- "Treatment of Atypical Pneumonia" 9:69, Issue 226, 1967 September 8; 1 of 3 (Box 127, Folder 4)
- "Treatment of Atypical Pneumonia [Sources, Reprints]" 9:69, Issue 226, 1967 September 8; 2 of 3 (Box 127, Folder 5)
- "Treatment of Atypical Pneumonia [Sources, Reprints]" 9:69, Issue 226, 1967 September 8; 3 of 3 (Box 127, Folder 6)
- "Haloperidol" 9:70, Issue 226, 1967 September 8; 1 of 6 (Box 127, Folder 7)
- "Haloperidol [Sources, Reprints]" 9:70, Issue 226, 1967 September 8; 2 of 6 (Box 127, Folder 8)
- "Haloperidol [Sources, Reprints]" 9:70, Issue 226, 1967 September 8; 3 of 6 (Box 127, Folder 9)
- "Haloperidol [Sources, Reprints]" 9:70, Issue 226, 1967 September 8; 4 of 6 (Box 127, Folder 10)
- "Haloperidol [Sources, Reprints]" 9:70, Issue 226, 1967 September 8; 5 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 1)
- "Haloperidol [Sources, Reprints]" 9:70, Issue 226, 1967 September 8; 6 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 2)